# **Santiago Lloret**

Regional Manager
APAC, MENA & Global Safety Projects

Email: santiago.lloret@outlook.com

Contact No: 085-7800-727

Address: 26 Compass Court South, Dublin 15
 LinkedIn: Linkedin.com/in/Santiago Lloret

## **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Enthusiastic and energetic Manager with +4 years of experience, oriented to achieve excellency through teamwork and empowerment based on streamlined operations, business strategy, efficiency, delivery of high-level performance and maintaining motivation in all levels of the structure.

Assertive, goal oriented and self-determined are the main characteristics of my personality.

My core values are work ethics, respect and dignity.

## **KNOWLEDGEABLE QUALIFICATIONS**

- Strong analytical, evaluation, project and team management skills
- Excellent oral and written communication skills (Spanish, English and Catalan fluent)
- Superior interpersonal and organisation skills
- Team player, goal oriented and able to work under pressure
- Has the ability and willingness to assume responsibility

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS AND STRENGTHS

Advanced skills on Microsoft Office applications particularly on MS Word, Excel, and PowerPoint

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **OOH Regional Manager**

May 2018 - Present

Covalen

Dublin, Ireland

## Responsibilities

- -Main responsible of the general operations of Asia Pacific, Middle East and Global Safety regions across evening and night shifts;
- -Delivery of SLA's and managing of 7 Team Leads, 5 Anchor Mentors, 6 Coach SME's and 104 Content Analysts across 17 markets;
- -Provide mentorship and career development for Team Leads;
- -Headcount estimation by measuring estimated workload and AHT;
- -Coordinate internal and external recruitment coverage;
- -Alignment and calibration with the client, internal verticals and support teams;
- -Optimize resources utilization and setting strategic processes to mitigate risks;
- -Management of Safety, Government, Language and Policy high priority escalations; and
- -Identify potential business opportunities for the growth of Cpl onsite and improve the service experience of our client counterpart.

#### Team Leader / L&D Manager

Oct 2016 - May 2018

Covalen

Dublin, Ireland

## **Team Lead Responsibilities**

- -Main responsible of the general operations of Asia Pacific region. Direct manager of 1 Team Coordinator, 1 Quality POC and 22 Content Analysts;
- -Ensuring metrics and SLAs are delivered to the client on time; and
- -Involved in staff mentoring and their career development/improvements.

## **L&D Manager Responsibilities**

- -Involved in launching the first L&D Structure in the Company; and
- -Responsible with the related administrative tasks of L&D Department (such as designing skillsets of trainings, ensuring high attendance and tracking of individuals' performance).

#### **Anchor Mentor / Team Coordinator**

Feb 2016 - Oct 2016

Covalen

Dublin, Ireland

#### Responsibilities

- -Main responsible of the workload distribution for Content Analysts, daily tasks for the team to accomplish and ensuring clients' requirements are met; and
- -Involved in staff mentoring and their career development/improvements.

## **Content Analyst**

Feb 2015 - Feb 2016

Covalen

Dublin, Ireland

#### Responsibilities

- -Assessment of contents in the client's platform and enforcement of the Company's Policies accordingly when this violated terms and conditions; and
- -All reviewed based on turnaround time, quality and productivity parameters.

#### **OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE**

Details available in Linkedin.com/in/Santiago Lloret

Customer Service Oct 2014 – Feb 2015

Persian Restaurants Ltd Dublin, Ireland

Store ManagerFeb 2013 – Oct 2014Casa Cruz, Cash & CarryGuadalajara, Mexico

Billing Service Advisor Jun 2012 – Feb 2013

Sidney Marketing Guadalajara, Mexico

ReceptionistJan 2011 – Jun 2012Grupo ICLARGuadalajara, Mexico

Customer Service RepresentativeJan 2010 – Jan 2011Hispanic Teleservices CorporationGuadalajara, Mexico

# **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Code Institute **2019 - Present** Full-Stack Web Development Dublin, Ireland

Certification

Universidad del Valle de Atemajac 2009 - 2012

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration Guadalajara, Mexico

BBA, International

## **CHARACTER REFERENCE**

Available upon request